<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<document-metadata version="1.0" xmlns="http://breeze.macromedia.com/ns/document-metadata" generator="Adobe Captivate 2">
<document-info>
	<title>ncu_library_tour</title>
	<summary></summary>
	<author>esalazar</author>
	<keywords>Adobe Captivate Project ncu_library_tour</keywords>
	<view-link href="ncu_library_tour_1.swf?slide={position}"/>
</document-info>
<section type="slide" position="1">
	<title>Notes</title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the NCU Databases link</text>

	<text>NCU Databases/Tools</text>

	<text>Ask a Librarian</text>

	<text>Services</text>

	<text>Research Help</text>

	<text>About us</text>

	<text>Welcome to NCU Library Tour.</text>
</content>

	<related-content>Welcome to the NCU Library Tour! This two-part tour introduces you to the major parts of the site. It is recommended that you spend some time on familiarizing yourself with the Library. Many resources are available to you for your research.     As you can see from the opening page there are may links for you to begin. Know that the site is divided into four categories: Databases/Tools, Research Help, Services and About Us.     Lastly, use the Ask a Librarian link on the far left corner of site to contact us for any of your research needs. We&apos;ll begin by going to the NCU Database page.  </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="2">
	<title>Notes1</title>

	<content>
	<text>NCU Databases page lists all of NCU&apos;s databases</text>

	<text>Navigation Trail</text>

	<text>Quick Links box</text>

	<text>Flash tutorial link</text>

	<text>Find scholarly articles, newspapers, magazines, books and much more. </text>
</content>

	<related-content>The NCU Database is the mosted visited page in the Library. Here is listed all of the major databases available to you for research. These databases contain scholarly journals, newspapers, magazines, dissertations, reviews, case studies, trade publications, dissertations, electronic books and more.     Note that this page provides a navigation trail and Quick Links box, which we will explore on the Find an Article page. Please take the time to read the database descriptions to better understand what a specific database offers. Lastly, flash tutorials are available to demonstrate how to the database. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="3">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the Find an Article link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="4">
	<title>Notes2</title>

	<content></content>

	<related-content>The Find an Article organizes databases by degree programs.  </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="5">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Let&apos;s take a look at Business</text>

	<text>Select the Business link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="6">
	<title>Notes3</title>

	<content>
	<text>ProQuest offers full-text</text>
</content>

	<related-content>The Business page offers business-specific databases. Each database is accompanied with a description and type of offering. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="7">
	<title>Notes4</title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the E-Journal Portal link</text>

	<text>Quick Links box</text>
</content>

	<related-content>The Quick Links box takes you the E-Journal portal which identifies all full-text journal available in the Library. This is an extremely helpful tool for doing research. Let&apos;s go ahead and click the e-journal for a quick viewing. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="8">
	<title>Notes5</title>

	<content>
	<text>Enter journal title here</text>

	<text>Browse for journals in a specific area</text>
</content>

	<related-content>This is the E-Journal Portal. Simply enter a journal title to see if it is available in our collection or select a topic area to browse for available electronic journals. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="9">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the Databases Index link</text>
</content>

	<related-content>Coming back to the Find an Article Business page, select the Databases Index page. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="10">
	<title>Notes6</title>

	<content>
	<text>The Database Index page appears</text>

	<text>NCU subscription database or freebie</text>
</content>

	<related-content>The Database Index page lists each individual database offered by the University as well as all free databases on the Web. You can sort by coverage and full-text availability. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="11">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the Find a Book link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="12">
	<title>Notes7</title>

	<content></content>

	<related-content>The Find a Book page lists resources that allow you to view electronic books as well as locate print books.</related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="13">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the Dissertation Resources link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="14">
	<title>Notes8</title>

	<content>
	<text>Locate NCU Dissertations here. </text>

	<text>Locate dissertations from North America here. </text>
</content>

	<related-content>The Dissertation Resources page offers links to full-text dissertations. Read full-text   dissertations from former NCU Learners by clicking the NCU Dissertations link or find    full-text dissertations from thousands of students in North America by clicking the   ProQuest Dissertation and Theses database. You can also read dissertation abstracts   from around the world by using the WorldCat Dissertation and Theses databases.   </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="15">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the Find Citation Help link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="16">
	<title>Notes9</title>

	<content>
	<text>NoodleTools helps you format your citations.</text>
</content>

	<related-content>The Find Citation Help page offers NoodleTools, a program that helps you format your citations into APA format. You will need to create a folder to get started. Other links on this page include TurnItIn, an appllcation that checks your essays for plagiarism. Be aware that your mentor might ask you to submit your paper to TurnItIn. The TurnItIn links on this page are tutorials on how to use it. Explore this page to learn about tools that can help you with APA. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="17">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the Databases FAQs link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="18">
	<title>Notes10</title>

	<content>
	<text>Click this link to submit a database problem form. </text>
</content>

	<related-content>Use the Database FAQs page if you&apos;re experiencing technical difficulties. Listed on this page are frequently asked questions about access issues to databases. If you need further assistance, then please complete a database problem form; this will help us better troubleshoot the problem.</related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="19">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the Reading Room  link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="20">
	<title>Notes15</title>

	<content></content>

	<related-content>The Reading Room offers periodicals for research and casual reading. This page and the   refernece collection page are places that might you want to visit when starting your   research.   </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="21">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the Course Guides link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="22">
	<title>Notes11</title>

	<content>
	<text>The Course Guides page appears</text>

	<text>Search box</text>
</content>

	<related-content>The Course Guides lists resources by specialization as well as individual courses. Use the Search box above to locate a guide for your course. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="23">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Click the Search button</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="25">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the OM7015 link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="26">
	<title>Notes12</title>

	<content>
	<text>Course guide addresses specific assignments</text>
</content>

	<related-content>As seen on this page, this guide address a specific assignment in for this course. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="27">
	<title></title>

	<content>
	<text>Select the Reference Collection link</text>
</content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="28">
	<title>Notes13</title>

	<content>
	<text>Locate encyclopedias, dictionaries, and more</text>
</content>

	<related-content>The Reference Collection page lists reference resources, such as encyclopedias, handbooks, dictionaries, thesauri, and more. This is good place to start research. </related-content>
</section>
<section type="slide" position="29">
	<title>Notes14</title>

	<content>
	<text>This ends the first half of the tour. Please see the Library Tour Part II.</text>
</content>

	<related-content>This ends the first half of the tour. Please see second part of Library Tour to continue. Thanks. </related-content>
</section>
</document-metadata>
